<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Brum Tech Scene</title><link>http://www.brumtechscene.co.uk/</link><description></description><atom:link href="http://www.brumtechscene.co.uk/feeds/stuart-langridge.rss.xml" rel="self"></atom:link><lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>Leigh Purnell</title><link>http://www.brumtechscene.co.uk/#leigh-purnell</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Brum Tech Scene Interviews are a series of video conversations with interesting and enlightening people involved with technology in some way in Birmingham. Leigh Purnell is founder of Petalite Battery, who are launching a crowdfunding campaign for their new external phone battery which charges in fifteen minutes.&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">Stuart Langridge</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2014 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>tag:www.brumtechscene.co.uk,2014-11-17:</guid></item><item><title>Dave Evans</title><link>http://www.brumtechscene.co.uk/#dave-evans</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Brum Tech Scene Interviews are a series of video conversations with interesting and enlightening people involved with technology in some way in Birmingham. This discussion is with Dave Evans: serial entrepreneur, .NET expert, and head of the nascent Xamarin user group in Birmingham.&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">Stuart Langridge</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2014 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>tag:www.brumtechscene.co.uk,2014-11-10:</guid></item><item><title>Ian Harrison</title><link>http://www.brumtechscene.co.uk/#ian-harrison</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Brum Tech Scene Interviews are a series of video conversations with interesting and enlightening people involved with technology in some way in Birmingham. This discussion is with Ian Harrison, co-curator of TEDxBrum, an independent TEDx event with a theme of "DIY" on November 8th 2014 at the Library of Birmingham.&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">Stuart Langridge</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2014 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>tag:www.brumtechscene.co.uk,2014-11-03:</guid></item><item><title>Matthew Somerville</title><link>http://www.brumtechscene.co.uk/#matthew-somerville</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Brum Tech Scene Interviews are a series of video conversations with interesting and enlightening people involved with technology in some way in Birmingham. This discussion is with Matthew Somerville, programmer for MySociety and founder of traintimes.org.uk and Theatricalia.&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">Stuart Langridge</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2014 05:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>tag:www.brumtechscene.co.uk,2014-10-27:</guid></item><item><title>Ryan Dean-Corke</title><link>http://www.brumtechscene.co.uk/#ryan-dean-corke</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Brum Tech Scene Interviews are a series of video conversations with interesting and enlightening people involved with technology in some way in Birmingham. This discussion is with Ryan Dean-Corke, designer for McCann Birmingham, formerly of SubStrakt, and part of the Good For Nothing Birmingham project.&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">Stuart Langridge</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 20 Oct 2014 05:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>tag:www.brumtechscene.co.uk,2014-10-20:</guid></item><item><title>Susannah Goh</title><link>http://www.brumtechscene.co.uk/#susannah-goh</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Brum Tech Scene Interviews are a series of video conversations with interesting and enlightening people involved with technology in some way in Birmingham. This discussion is with Susannah Goh, Innovative Health and Digital Media lead at Birmingham Science City, chair of the Open Data Forum, and skateboarder.&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">Stuart Langridge</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2014 05:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>tag:www.brumtechscene.co.uk,2014-10-13:</guid></item><item><title>Andy Higgs</title><link>http://www.brumtechscene.co.uk/#andy-higgs</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Brum Tech Scene Interviews are a series of video conversations with interesting and enlightening people involved with technology in some way in Birmingham. This discussion is with Andy Higgs, co-founder of the Badego design group and Akkroo.&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">Stuart Langridge</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2014 05:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>tag:www.brumtechscene.co.uk,2014-10-06:</guid></item><item><title>Jess Rose</title><link>http://www.brumtechscene.co.uk/#jess-rose</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Brum Tech Scene Interviews are a series of video conversations with interesting and enlightening people involved with technology in some way in Birmingham. This discussion is with Jess Rose, founder of Birmingham Open Code and Ladies Who Code Birmingham.&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">Stuart Langridge</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2014 05:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>tag:www.brumtechscene.co.uk,2014-09-29:</guid></item><item><title>Bruce Lawson</title><link>http://www.brumtechscene.co.uk/#bruce-lawson</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Brum Tech Scene Interviews are a series of video conversations with interesting and enlightening people involved with technology in some way in Birmingham. This discussion is with Bruce Lawson, open standards advocate for the Opera web browser.&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">Stuart Langridge</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2014 05:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>tag:www.brumtechscene.co.uk,2014-09-22:</guid></item><item><title>Simon Jenner</title><link>http://www.brumtechscene.co.uk/#simon-jenner</link><description>&lt;p&gt;The Brum Tech Scene Interviews are a series of video conversations with interesting and enlightening people involved with technology in some way in Birmingham. Our inaugural interview is with Simon Jenner, head of Oxygen Startups and co-founder of Silicon Canal.&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">Stuart Langridge</dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2014 15:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>tag:www.brumtechscene.co.uk,2014-09-14:</guid></item><item><title>Stuart Langridge</title><link>http://www.brumtechscene.co.uk/#stuart-langridge</link><description>&lt;p&gt;An introduction to the Brum Tech Scene interviews, by Stuart Langridge.&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">Stuart Langridge</dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2014 14:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>tag:www.brumtechscene.co.uk,2014-09-14:</guid></item></channel></rss>